♪ ♪
♪ NICE GIRLS NOT ONE
WITH A DEFECT, ♪
♪ CELLOPHANE SHRINK-WRAPPED,
SO CORRECT. ♪
♪ RED DOGS UNDER
ILLEGAL LEGS ♪
♪ ♪
♪ SHE LOOKS SO GOOD THAT HE
GETS DOWN AND BEGS. ♪
♪ SHE IS
WATCHING THE DETECTIVES ♪
♪ "OOH, HE'S SO CUTE!" ♪
♪ SHE IS WATCHING
THE DETECTIVES ♪
♪ WHEN THEY SHOOT,
SHOOT, SHOOT, SHOOT. ♪
♪ THEY BEAT HIM UP UNTIL
THE TEARDROPS START, ♪
♪ BUT HE CAN'T BE WOUNDED
'CAUSE HE'S GOT NO HEART. ♪
♪ ♪
♪ LONG SHOT OF THAT
JUMPING SIGN ♪
♪ VISIBLE SHIVERS RUNNING
DOWN MY SPINE. ♪
♪ CUT THE BABY TAKING
OFF HER CLOTHES. ♪
♪ CLOSE-UP OF THE SIGN THAT
SAYS,"WE NEVER CLOSE" ♪
♪ YOU SNATCH A TUNE, YOU
A MATCH A CIGARETTE, ♪
♪ SHE PULLS THE EYES OUT
WITH A FACE LIKE A MAGNET. ♪
♪ I DON'T KNOW HOW MUCH
MORE OF THIS I CAN TAKE. ♪
♪ SHE'S FILING HER NAILS WHILE
THEY'RE DRAGGING THE LAKE. ♪
♪ SHE IS
WATCHING THE DETECTIVES ♪
♪ "OOH, HE'S SO CUTE!" ♪
♪ SHE IS
WATCHING THE DETECTIVES ♪
♪ OH WHEN THEY SHOOT,
SHOOT, SHOOT, SHOOT. ♪
♪ THEY BEAT HIM UP UNTIL
THE TEARDROPS START, ♪
♪ BUT HE CAN'T BE WOUNDED
'CAUSE HE'S GOT NO HEART. ♪
♪ ♪
♪ YOU THINK YOU'RE ALONE UNTIL
YOU REALIZE YOU'RE IN IT. ♪
♪ NOW FEAR IS HERE TO STAY.
LOVE IS HERE FOR A VISIT. ♪
♪ THEY CALL IT INSTANT JUSTICE
WHEN IT'S PAST THE LEGAL LIMIT ♪
♪ SOMEONE'S SCRATCHING AT THE
WINDOW. I WONDER WHO IS IT? ♪
♪ THE DETECTIVES COME TO CHECK
IF YOU BELONG TO THE PARENTS ♪
♪ WHO ARE READY TO HEAR THE
WORST ABOUT THEIR DAUGHTER'S
DISAPPEARANCE ♪
♪ THOUGH IT NEARLY TOOK A
MIRACLE TO GET YOU TO STAY ♪
♪ IT ONLY TOOK MY LITTLE
FINGERS TO BLOW YOU AWAY ♪
♪ ♪
♪ JUST LIKE
WATCHING THE DETECTIVES ♪
♪ DON'T GET CUTE!" ♪
♪ IT'S JUST LIKE
WATCHING THE DETECTIVES. ♪
♪ I GET SO ANGRY WHEN
THE TEARDROPS START, ♪
♪ BUT HE CAN'T BE WOUNDED
'CAUSE HE'S GOT NO HEART. ♪
♪ ♪
♪ WATCHING THE DETECTIVES. ♪
♪ IT'S JUST LIKE
WATCHING THE DETECTIVES ♪
♪ ♪
♪ WATCHING THE DETECTIVES. ♪